Bridge Line Historical Society; Collection mss129
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Maps, Blueprints, and Drawings, 1870-2004; 2; 613 items
  - Right of Way and Track Map: Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway Company: Johnsonville to Schuylerville, Station 1048+03 to Station 1100+40 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 494)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001342
  - Right of Way and Track Map: Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway Company: Johnsonville to Schuylerville, Station 728+35 to Station 780+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 534)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001269
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Albany Terminal, Station 0+00 to Station 46+68.3 and Albany Terminal, Water Street Branch, Station 0+00 to Station 10+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 501)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001350
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division Ausable Branch, Ausable Forks to South Junction, Station 765+67 to Station 871+30 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 497)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001346
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division Baldwin Branch, Delano Junction to Baldwin, Station 0+00 to Station 125+50 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 527)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001330
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division Main Line Lake Station Whitehall to Canada Line, Station 5797+94 to Station 5899+54 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 538)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001331
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division Main Line, Lake Station Whitehall to Canada Line, Station 5059+01 to Station 5164+60 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 531)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001335
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division Main Line, Lake Station Whitehall to Canada Line, Station 5164+60 to Station 5270+15 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 539)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001276
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division Main Line, Lake Station Whitehall to Canada Line, Station 5375+71 to Station 5481+29 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 532)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001280
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division Main Line, Lake Station Whitehall to Canada Line, Station 5693+39 to Station 5797+94 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 537)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001332
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division Main Line, Lake Station, Whitehall to Canada Line, Station 2842+50 to Station 2948+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 451)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001381
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division Main Line, Lake Station, Whitehall to Canada Line, Station 5164+60 to Station 5270+15 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 514)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001334
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division Main Line, Lake Station, Whitehall to Canada Line, Station 5897+00 to Station 5959+79 (Reproduction of 1924 Map), Undated (Map-tube 505)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001272
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division, Chateauguay Branch, Dannemora to Bluff Point, Station 0+00 to Station 102+21 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 442)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001383
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division, Chateauguay Branch, Dannemora to Bluff Point; Station 3579+68 to Station 3896+18 (Three Sheets) (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 133)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001259-BLA001261
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Champlain Division, Chateauguay Branch, Lake Placid to Dannemora (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 193)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001256-BLA001258
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Buttonwood Junction to Hudson, Station 203+40 to Station 258+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 409)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001384
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Green Ridge to Carbondale; Station 1120+62.7 to Station 1173+35.0 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 135)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001174
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Green Ridge to Carbondale, Station 1437+96.4 to Station 1490+81.9 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 408)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001386
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Green Ridge to Carbondale, Station 1490+81.9 to Station 1543+15.4 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 407)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001387
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Green Ridge to Carbondale, Station 1648+65.1 to Station 1701+27.1 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 169)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001262
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Green Ridge to Carbondale, Station 1859+58.9 to Station 1912+50.0 (Reproduction of 1919 Map), Undated (Map-tube 516)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA00000874
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Wilkes Barre to Green Ridge, Station 65+32 to Station 118+35.3 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 441)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001389
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Wilkes-Barre to Green Ridge, Station 0+00 to Station 12+51.9 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 512)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000878
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Wilkes-Barre to Green Ridge, Station 118+35.3 to Station 170+12.3 (2 sheets) (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 427)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001390
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Wilkes-Barre to Green Ridge; Station 540+31.1 to Station 593+15.3 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 168)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001265
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Wilkes-Barre to Green Ridge; Station 963+12.3 to Station 1015+20.9 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 161)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001193
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line; Green Ridge to Carbondale, Station 1701+27.1 to Station 1753+97.0 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 175)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001263
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line; Green Ridge to Carbondale, Station 1859+58.9 to Station 1912+500 (Reproduction of 1919 Map), Undated (Map-tube 180)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001176
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line; Jefferson Junction to State Line, Station 3772+17.2 to Station 3824+92.3 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 194)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001264
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division, Green Ridge to Carbondale; Station 1806+92.5 to Station 1859+58.9 (Reproduction of 1945 Map), Undated (Map-tube 137)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001190
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division, Main Line Green Ridge to Carbondale; Station 1126+01.7 to Station 1278+95.1 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 141)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001175
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division, Plymouth No. 3 Branch, Station 102+00 to Station 125+42.05 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 511)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000881
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division, Scranton Branch, Station 0+00 to Station 27+19.49 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 165)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001194
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Main Line, Green Ridge to Carbondale; Station 1278+95.1 to Station 1331+60.8 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 157)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001191
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Adirondack Branch, Saratoga Springs to North Creek, Station 3008+75 to Station 3110+98 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 509)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001329
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Adirondack Branch, Saratoga Springs to North Creek, Station 477+63 to Station 583+17 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 535)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001270
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division George Branch, Fort Edward to Lake George, Station 240+97 to Station 293+63.9 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 246)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001328
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Green Island Branch, Watervliet Junction to Troy, Station 0+00 to Station 59+68.9 and Saratoga Division Troy Branch, Green Island to Waterford Junction, Station 0+00 to Station 9+63 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 526)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001339
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Lake George Branch, Fort Edward to Lake George, Station 0+00 to Station 29+43.5 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 510)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001267
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Lake George Branch, Fort Edward to Lake George, Station 29+43.5 to Station 82+22.0 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 508)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001283
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Albany to Waterford Junction, Station 103+76 to Station 158+40 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 506)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001271
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Albany to Waterford Junction, Station 0+00 to Station 51+50 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 529)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001338
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Albany to Waterford Junction, Station 263+92.5 to Station 316+85 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 540)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001275
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Albany to Waterford Junction, Station 369+40 to Station 422+28 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 571)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001274
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Albany to Waterford Junction; Station 158+40 to Station 211+80.5 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 495)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001343
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Albany to Waterford Junction; Station 369+40 to Station 422+28 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 162)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001215
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Saratoga Springs to Lake Station, Station 2532+39 to Station 2585+51.5 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 528)
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Saratoga Springs to Lake Station, Station 2585+51.5 to Station 2638+23.8 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 515)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001333
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Saratoga Springs to Lake Station, Station 2902+51 to Station 2955+43 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 507)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001268
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Saratoga Springs to Lake Station, Station 4011+13 to Station 4063+60 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 524)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000932
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Waterford Junction to Ballston, Station 1001+79 to Station 1055+40 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 521)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000929
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Waterford Junction to Ballston, Station 1159+90 to Station 1212+56 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 536)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001273
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Waterford Junction to Ballston, Station 1633+83.5 to Station 1665+11.5 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 513)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001325
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Waterford Junction to Ballston, Station 948+28 to Station 101+79 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 502)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001351
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line, Waterford Junction to Ballston; Station 1001+79 to Station 1055+40 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 138)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001199
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line; Saratoga Springs to Lake Station, Station 2848+87 to Station 2902+51 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 172)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001181
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line; Waterford Junction to Ballston, Station 1001+79 to Station 1055+40, 1970 (Map-tube 189)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001198
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Main Line; Waterford Junction to Ballston, Station 1055+40 to Station 1107+22 (Reproduction of 1916), Undated (Map-tube 187)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001248
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Salem Branch; Greenwich to Greenwich Junction, Station 423+24.7 to Station 528+20 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 174)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001246
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division, Ballston Branch, Schenectady to Ballston Spa, Sand Bank Track; Station 36+00 to Station 36+55.5 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 155)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001253
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division, Ballston Branch, Schenectady to Ballston Spa; Station 0+00 to Station 36+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 140)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001180
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division, Ballston Branch, Schenectady to Ballston Spa; Station 53+30 to Station 106+10 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 150)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001197
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division, Main Line Albany to Waterford Junction; Station 0+00 to Station 51+50 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 139)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001196
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division, Washington Branch in Vermont, True Blue Branch; Station 90+00 to Station 151+68.5 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 136)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001213
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division, Washington Branch in Vermont; Station 0+00 to Station 90+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 131)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001212
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division, Washington Branch in Vermont; Station 3081+643 to Station 3135+01 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 163)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001211
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Station 0+00 to Station 30+97 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 499)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001345
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Cherry Valley Branch, Cherry Valley to Cherry Valley Junction, Station 437+83 to Station 491+08 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 171)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: 001172
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Cherry Valley Branch, Cherry Valley to Cherry Valley Junction; Station 649+55 to Station 702+36 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 152)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001170
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Cherry Valley Branch, Cherry Valley to Cherry Valley Junction; Station 913+46 to Station 964+96 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 170)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001171
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 25+57 to Station 78+37 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 444)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001160
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 25+57 to Station 78+37 (Reproduction of 1928 Map), Undated (Map-tube 436)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001161
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 25+57 to Station 78+37 (Reproduction of 1948 Map), Undated (Map-tube 412)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001363
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 3032+35.7 to Station 3085+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 518)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000863
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 3085+00 to Station 3137+65 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 519)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000862
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 3137+65 to Station 3190+25 (Reproduction of 1929 Map), Undated (Map-tube 517)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000864
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 3190+25 to Station 3242+99 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 503)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001349
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 3454+005 to Station 3506+64 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 452)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001380
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 3770+24 to Station 3822+90.5 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 498)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001347
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 7411 to 04.4 to Station 7462+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 530)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001336
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 78+37 to Station 131+19 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 453)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000427
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany; Station 1870+840 to Station 1923+49.4 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 153)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001182
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany; Station 3085+00 to Station 3137+65, 1950 (Map-tube 143)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001189
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany; Station 3190+25 to Station 3241+99 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 151)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001173
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany; Station 6565+95 to Station 6618+56 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 149)
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany; Station 6618+56 to Station 6671+44.3 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 158)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001210
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line; Binghamton to Albany, Oneonta Yards (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 181)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001188
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line; Binghamton to Albany, Station 131+19 to Station 184+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 173)